<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Share on Charles Chin's Blog</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/categories/share/</link><description>Recent content in Share on Charles Chin's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2006 - 2025 &lt;span class='inline-block'>&lt;a href='https://www.eallion.com/copyright/' target='_blank'>eallion.com&lt;/a> All Rights Reserved&lt;/span>. &lt;span class='inline-block'>&lt;a href='https://beian.miit.gov.cn/' target='_blank'>浙ICP备16031768号-2&lt;/a>&lt;/span></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:08:22 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.eallion.com/en/categories/share/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><follow_challenge><feedId>42331815237783556</feedId><userId>41909911558319104</userId></follow_challenge><item><title>Sonnet 141</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-141/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:08:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-141/</guid><description>The article discusses Sonnet 141 by William Shakespeare, which explores the speaker&amp;rsquo;s unconventional love for someone despite their flaws. The speaker explains that they do not love with their eyes or other senses but with their heart. They acknowledge the person&amp;rsquo;s imperfections but still choose to adore them. The article also provides a Chinese translation of the sonnet.</description></item><item><title>Sonnet 116</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-116/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 16:08:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-116/</guid><description>The article discusses Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s Sonnet 116, which explores the concept of true love. It emphasizes that love is unchanging and steadfast, unaffected by time or external circumstances. The sonnet argues that if anyone can prove this idea wrong, then Shakespeare never wrote and no one has ever truly loved.</description></item><item><title>The Declaration of Independence</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/the-declaration-of-independence/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:53:51 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/the-declaration-of-independence/</guid><description>The article summarizes the content of &amp;ldquo;The Declaration of Independence&amp;rdquo; which was adopted by the thirteen united States of America on July 4, 1776. It declares that all men are created equal and have certain unalienable rights. It lists a series of grievances against King George III and asserts that the colonies are now free and independent states with the power to govern themselves. The signatories pledge their lives, fortunes, and honor to support this declaration.</description></item><item><title>Love at First Sight</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/love-at-first-sight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:20:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/love-at-first-sight/</guid><description>The article discusses the concept of love at first sight and how two people can feel a strong connection without knowing each other. It explores the idea that fate has been playing with them, bringing them closer but also pushing them further apart. The author reflects on possible moments in their lives where they could have crossed paths, but ultimately concludes that every beginning is just a continuation and that destiny is always unfolding.</description></item></channel></rss>