<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eallion on Charles Chin's Blog</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/authors/eallion/</link><description>Recent content in Eallion on Charles Chin's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2006 - 2025 &lt;span class='inline-block'>&lt;a href='https://www.eallion.com/copyright/' target='_blank'>eallion.com&lt;/a> All Rights Reserved&lt;/span>. &lt;span class='inline-block'>&lt;a href='https://beian.miit.gov.cn/' target='_blank'>浙ICP备16031768号-2&lt;/a>&lt;/span></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 20:43:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.eallion.com/en/authors/eallion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><follow_challenge><feedId>42331815237783556</feedId><userId>41909911558319104</userId></follow_challenge><item><title>Chrome Plugin Update Url Cleaner</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/chrome-plugin-update-url-cleaner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 20:43:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/chrome-plugin-update-url-cleaner/</guid><description>This article introduces a Chrome extension called URL Cleaner. This extension can convert the current tab&amp;rsquo;s URL into a clean URL. The author developed an e-commerce plugin 15 years ago to purify Taobao links. He found that at that time, designers and customer service representatives did not have a good understanding of URL mechanisms, which resulted in overly long links for store decoration and when sending to customers. Therefore, he redeveloped this plugin and updated it to migrate to Manifest V3, change the plugin name, add a whitelist settings feature, and update the icon. The built-in whitelist now supports multiple common websites by default and also supports internationalization (i18n). Finally, the author mentioned that after releasing version 2.0.0, he learned about the CSS property field-sizing and made optimizations, leading to the release of version 2.0.1. Interested readers can visit the Chrome Web Store to install and experience the plugin.</description></item><item><title>Sonnet 141</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-141/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:08:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-141/</guid><description>The article discusses Sonnet 141 by William Shakespeare, which explores the speaker&amp;rsquo;s unconventional love for someone despite their flaws. The speaker explains that they do not love with their eyes or other senses but with their heart. They acknowledge the person&amp;rsquo;s imperfections but still choose to adore them. The article also provides a Chinese translation of the sonnet.</description></item><item><title>Sonnet 116</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-116/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 16:08:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/sonnet-116/</guid><description>The article discusses Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s Sonnet 116, which explores the concept of true love. It emphasizes that love is unchanging and steadfast, unaffected by time or external circumstances. The sonnet argues that if anyone can prove this idea wrong, then Shakespeare never wrote and no one has ever truly loved.</description></item><item><title>I Have a Dream</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/i-have-a-dream/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:02:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/i-have-a-dream/</guid><description>The article discusses the ongoing struggle for freedom and equality for African Americans in America. It highlights the continued oppression faced by black people, including segregation and discrimination. The author emphasizes the need to fulfill the promises of democracy and justice, urging for immediate action rather than gradual change. The article concludes with a powerful vision of a future where all races can live together in harmony and freedom.</description></item><item><title>The Declaration of Independence</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/the-declaration-of-independence/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:53:51 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/the-declaration-of-independence/</guid><description>The article summarizes the content of &amp;ldquo;The Declaration of Independence&amp;rdquo; which was adopted by the thirteen united States of America on July 4, 1776. It declares that all men are created equal and have certain unalienable rights. It lists a series of grievances against King George III and asserts that the colonies are now free and independent states with the power to govern themselves. The signatories pledge their lives, fortunes, and honor to support this declaration.</description></item><item><title>Love at First Sight</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/love-at-first-sight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:20:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/love-at-first-sight/</guid><description>The article discusses the concept of love at first sight and how two people can feel a strong connection without knowing each other. It explores the idea that fate has been playing with them, bringing them closer but also pushing them further apart. The author reflects on possible moments in their lives where they could have crossed paths, but ultimately concludes that every beginning is just a continuation and that destiny is always unfolding.</description></item><item><title>Learn to blog in English</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/english/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/english/</guid><description>&lt;p>Learn to write an English blog from now on.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>