<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chrome on Charles Chin's Blog</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/tags/chrome/</link><description>Recent content in Chrome on Charles Chin's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2006 - 2025 &lt;span class='inline-block'>&lt;a href='https://www.eallion.com/copyright/' target='_blank'>eallion.com&lt;/a> All Rights Reserved&lt;/span>. &lt;span class='inline-block'>&lt;a href='https://beian.miit.gov.cn/' target='_blank'>浙ICP备16031768号-2&lt;/a>&lt;/span></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 20:43:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.eallion.com/en/tags/chrome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><follow_challenge><feedId>42331815237783556</feedId><userId>41909911558319104</userId></follow_challenge><item><title>Chrome Plugin Update Url Cleaner</title><link>https://www.eallion.com/en/chrome-plugin-update-url-cleaner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 20:43:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.eallion.com/en/chrome-plugin-update-url-cleaner/</guid><description>This article introduces a Chrome extension called URL Cleaner. This extension can convert the current tab&amp;rsquo;s URL into a clean URL. The author developed an e-commerce plugin 15 years ago to purify Taobao links. He found that at that time, designers and customer service representatives did not have a good understanding of URL mechanisms, which resulted in overly long links for store decoration and when sending to customers. Therefore, he redeveloped this plugin and updated it to migrate to Manifest V3, change the plugin name, add a whitelist settings feature, and update the icon. The built-in whitelist now supports multiple common websites by default and also supports internationalization (i18n). Finally, the author mentioned that after releasing version 2.0.0, he learned about the CSS property field-sizing and made optimizations, leading to the release of version 2.0.1. Interested readers can visit the Chrome Web Store to install and experience the plugin.</description></item></channel></rss>